

talented team, I consistently delivered high-quality solutions

§ 9727084546 

☐ shubham.webdev3@gmail.com 

☐ Skype id: live:7f2f56a56269f36f

#### **Profiles**

😝 /Shubh Facebook

**♥** /Shubham Upwork

#### Summary

Certified Web Developer with 7+ years of experience who is comfortable working with HTML, CSS, Liquid, MySQL, Tailwind, Materialize, SaaS, Semantic UI, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and Laravel. And specializes in responsive, mobilefriendly websites, crafting custom themes, modifying existing themes and plugins, optimizing SEO, and writing custom code. From a design concept to a polished and professional site, I can help you or your business bring your vision to life and provide ongoing maintenance and updates.

#### **Experience**

#### **Limitless Solutions**

Web developer

March 2017 - Feb 2021

During my tenure at Limitless Solutions from March 2017 to February 2021, I had the opportunity to contribute to a wide range of WordPress and Shopify development projects. I leveraged my expertise in WordPress to create custom websites, develop themes, and optimize functionality to meet clients' unique requirements. Working collaboratively with a

#### CodeStrokes

Sr. Web developer

March 2021- Jan 2023

In March 2021, I transitioned to the role of Senior Web Developer at CodeStrokes, a progressive and dynamic company. Here, I took on more advanced responsibilities, leading and mentoring a team of developers while tackling complex web development projects. With a focus on delivering cutting-edge solutions, I utilized my strong problem-solving skills and in-depth knowledge of WordPress to create seamless user experiences, optimize website performance, and enhance overall functionality.

#### **Projects**

#### SHOPIFY

Shopify projects:

#### **BLEAME**

https://bleame.com/

#### NOOD

https://trynood.com/

#### ANCESTRAL SUPPLEMENTS

that surpassed client expectations.

https://ancestralsupplements.com/

# WISE WELL

https://www.wisewell.com/

## TWISG AND HONEY

https://www.twigsandhoney.com/

#### WORDPRESS

Wordpress projects:

#### STONE SOCIETE

https://www.stonesociete.ca/

#### **CUSTOM SOCKS**

https://www.customsockscanada.com/

## **GREGCO CONSTRUCTION**

https://www.gregcoconstruction.com/

## **SHIFT POSTS**

https://shiftposts.com/

## **CLIX PLUS**

https://www.clixplus.com/

## **Education**

## Agarwal Vidhya Vihar

Completed my schooling from the CBSE board.

#### (10+2)VNSGU

Computer Science

B.tech

Done my engineering in technology from VNSGU in Surat.

Cleared with 82%

## Skills

## Languages:

HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, Liquid, Tailwind, Materialize, SaaS, Semantic UI, and Bootstrap

## **Database:** MvSOL

• • • • 0

## **Graphic Designing:**

Photoshop, XD, Illustrator, Figma

## WordPress Builders:

Divi, Elementor, Visual Composer, WP Bakery, Themify, Avada, Gutenberg

## **Shopify Builders:**

Shogun, Pagefly, Zipify

## **Interests**

Learning new things

Listening to music

Learning new skills

Visiting new places

## Languages

. . . .

Gujarati

English

Hindi

Native language

Marathi

• • • 0 0